EMMALYN MADELO DAGARAG



San Isidro Gigaquit, Surigao Del Norte, Philippines ±639092808122 | emmalyndagarag022@gmail.com

Objective

To be involved in work where I can utilize skills and creatively involved with system that effectively contributes to the growth of organization. To expand my knowledge and capabilities of working. Responsible and challenging entry level. Open to new ideas.

Experience

Hong Kong DH/Caregiver

November 2019 - August 2022

Domestic Helper/Caregiver

A domestic worker is a person who works within the employer's household.

Domestic workers perform a variety of household services for an individual or a family, from providing care for children and elderly dependents to housekeeping, including cleaning and household maintenance.

Other Responsibilities may including

- Assisting with personal care, which include bathroom function.
- Bathing,grooming,dressing and eating
- Providing medication remember and appointment reminder, monitor the baby or elderly
- Performing light shousekeeping task (dusting,vacuuming,making beds,changing lines,taking out trash,cleaning bathroom, kitchen and ect.)
- providing companionship and conversation
- running errands

First Midio Korean Selection

October 2017 - August 2019

Cashier/Saleslady

Greet the costumers where entering or leaving the shop, count money in cash drawers at the beginning of shifts to ensure that amounts are correct and that there is adequate change,

- Receive payment by cash,
- Check credit cards,
- Voucher, or automatic debits,
- Issue receipts, Refunds, credits, or
- Change due to customers.

Park Way Mall

September 2013 - May 2014

Cashier

Greet the costumers where entering or leaving the shop, count money in cash drawers at the beginning of shifts to ensure that amounts are correct and that there is adequate change,

- Receive payment by cash,
- Check credit cards.
- Voucher, or automatic debits,
- o Issue receipts, Refunds, credits, or
- Change due to customers.

Education

• Icon Medical Group Hong Kong 2022 June Caregiver

• TESDA 2019 August

Domestic Work NC2

• St. Paul University Surigao Undergraduate

BS Hotel and Restaurant Management

• Gigaquit National School Of Home Industry 2008-2009

• San Isidro Elementary School 2004-2005

Skills

 Computer Literate / Time Management / Initiative / Organized / Negotiation / Strategic Planning / Work Underpressure / Multi-Tasking / Ability to work in various environments / Work and Physical Capabilities / Ability to work long hours with repetitive ttasks / Household work / Planting & Harvesting / Team Player / Reliability to Work

Personal Details

Date of Birth : 02/feb/1991

Marital Status : Single
Nationality : Filipino
Ago : 21

• Age : 31

Child : Paul Gabriel D. Aplan

Additional Information

CERTIFICATE:

*Domestic Work NC2

*Certificate in Caregiving

*Assured Professional Certificate in Caregiving

*Certificate in First Aid and Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation(CPR) with Automated External Defibrillator (AED)

*Certificate in Caregiving Level2

Summary

My goals have always been to do well with all my accomplishments and to be productive with all
that I achieve. Skilled Care Provider assisting Baby or elderly, convalescents,or persons with
disabilities with daily living activities in-home or within a care facility. Keep house by making beds,
doing laundry, washing dishes, and preparing meals. Advise families and healthcare team
regarding health concerns, nutrition, cleanliness, and household activities.
 Complete domestic duties, help the employer with self-care and hygiene, and provide
companionship. Experienced working with the baby, with skill anticipating and proactively
addressing client needs. Friendly and engaging with strong attention to detail. Motivate to learn
grow and excel to customer service.